You cannot defeat us, you cannot slow us,
you cannot stop us, you cannot deter us.
We will carry Charlie and Erica in our heart
every single day and fight that much harder
because of what you did to us.
You have no idea the dragon you have awakened.
You have no idea how determined we will be
to save this civilization, to save the West,
to save this Republic because our children are strong
and our grandchildren will be strong
and our children's children's children will be strong.
And what will you leave behind?
Nothing, nothing.
To our enemies, you have nothing to give,
you have nothing to offer, you have nothing to share,
but bitterness.
We have beauty, we have light, we have goodness,
we have determination, we have vision, we have strength.
We've built the world that we inhabit now,
generation by generation, and we will defend this world.
We will defend goodness, we will defend light,
we will defend virtue.
You cannot terrify us, you cannot frighten us,
you cannot threaten us because we are on the side of goodness,
we are on the side of God.
And to my friend, Charlie, to my brother, Charlie,
I know you are looking at us right now.
I know you're watching Erica right now.
I know you're watching your children right now.